https://www.marinoware.com/terms-of-use/

16 Nov 2020
SureBoard Floor combines the strength of steel with structural sheathing panel substrate. Its composite characteristics
...read more
Easily Construct partition and chase walls with high STC ratings!
5 Oct 2020
Save time with Sound|Guard stud. A factory assembled acoustically decoupled steel stud. Sound|Guard installs just
...read more
Terms & Conditions
Services and Conditions of Use of this web site (the “Website”):
In maintaining the Website, we (“Ware Industries, Inc. d/b/a Marino\WARE, d/b/a American Strip Steel, d/b/a Marino\WARE Design Group”) agree to provide you with information and other services that we may decide to offer, subject to the terms of this agreement. Upon notice published through the Website, we may modify this agreement at any time. You agree and continue to agree to use the Website in a manner consistent with all applicable laws and regulations and in accordance with the terms and conditions set out in the policies and guidelines outlined below. Please note that you will be referred to as ‘customer’ in this agreement.
Rules For Online Conduct
By using the Website, you agree that you will not attempt to undermine the integrity of the Website in any way.
Limitation of Liability and Warranty
CUSTOMER AGREES THAT USE OF THE WEBSITE IS ENTIRELY AT CUSTOMER’S OWN RISK. GOODS AND SERVICES PROVIDED ON THE WEBSITE ARE ‘AS IS,’ WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ANY WARRANTY FOR INFORMATION, SERVICES, UNINTERRUPTED ACCESS, OR PRODUCTS PROVIDED THROUGH OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE WEBSITE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION THE RESULTS OBTAINED THROUGH THE WEBSITE AND LINKS THAT APPEAR ON THE WEBSITE. SPECIFICALLY, WE DISCLAIM ANY AND ALL WARRANTIES, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION: 1) ANY WARRANTIES CONCERNING THE AVAILABILITY, ACCURACY OR CONTENT OF INFORMATION, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES; AND 2) ANY WARRANTIES OF TITLE OR WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
THIS DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY APPLIES TO ANY DAMAGES OR INJURY CAUSED BY ANY FAILURE OF PERFORMANCE, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DELETION, DEFECT, DELAY IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER VIRUS, COMMUNICATION LINE FAILURE, THEFT OR DESTRUCTION OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO, ALTERATION OF, OR USE OF RECORD, WHETHER FOR BREACH OF CONTRACT, TORTIOUS BEHAVIOR, NEGLIGENCE, OR UNDER ANY OTHER CAUSE OF ACTION. CUSTOMER SPECIFICALLY ACKNOWLEDGES THE SERVICE IS NOT LIABLE FOR THE DEFAMATORY, OFFENSIVE OR ILLEGAL CONDUCT OF OTHER CUSTOMERS OR THIRD-PARTIES AND THAT THE RISK OF INJURY FROM THE FOREGOING RESTS ENTIRELY WITH CUSTOMER.
NEITHER MARINO\WARE NOR ANY OF ITS AGENTS, AFFILIATES OR CONTENT PROVIDERS SHALL BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF USE OF THE WEBSITE OR INABILITY TO GAIN ACCESS TO OR USE THE WEBSITE OR OUT OF ANY BREACH OF ANY WARRANTY. CUSTOMER HEREBY ACKNOWLEDGES THAT THE PROVISIONS OF THIS SECTION SHALL APPLY TO ALL CONTENT ON THE SERVICE.
Trademarks
All trademarks appearing on the Website are trademarks of their respective owners.
Privacy Statement and Policy
We (“Ware Industries, Inc. d/b/a Marino\WARE, d/b/a American Strip Steel, d/b/a Marino/WARE Design Group”) have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site (the “Website”).
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.
Our site’s registration form requires users to give us contact information, like their name and email address, and unique identifiers. We may use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company. The customer’s contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary if they have subscribed to the mail list. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings by choosing to un-subscribe. Unique identifiers are collected to verify the user’s identity and for use in our record system.
Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor’s contact information and unique identifiers. Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. The customer’s contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings. Unique identifiers are collected from Website visitors to verify the user’s identity.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All data is protected using the most advanced methods available. We do not store financial information like credit card numbers or personal information like social security numbers on this site.
Unsubscribe or Opt-Out
All users and/or visitors to the Website have the option to discontinue receiving communications from us and/or reserve the right to discontinue receiving communications by way of email or newsletters. To discontinue or unsubscribe to the Website, please send an email that you want to unsubscribe to marketing@marinoware.com.
Links to Other Web Sites
The Website does contain links to other websites. Marino\WARE does not claim nor accept responsibility for any privacy policies, practices and/or procedures of other such websites. Therefore, we encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave the Website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies only to the Website.
Marinoware
Products
Resource Center
Product Videos
CAD LIBRARY / Specs
LITERATURE / Test Data
Order Literature
SDS
